blumhouse.com 2017-11-02

# Privacy Policy – Blumhouse.com

### BLUMHOUSE.COM PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: 10/1/2015.

### INTRODUCTION.

This Website, which is located at the domain Blumhouse.com and includes any content, functionality, services and features made available from or through this Website, including any subdomains in this Website (collectively, this “Website”), is operated by Blumhouse Entertainment, Inc. (together with its parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies, collectively, “Blumhouse.com” or “we” or “our” or “us”). Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Terms and Conditions of Use and Service for this Website, and describes the types of information we may collect from you and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining and protecting such information, what we may do with it and how we intend to maintain and protect it, with whom we may share it or how we may disclose it, and how you can correct or change such information.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect:

  * on this Website, _including webpages, interactive features and applications;_
  * in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website;
  * through mobile and desktop applications you may download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website;
  * when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline (other than as provided in Section 1) or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Blumhouse or any third party;
  * any third party, including through any application or content (such as advertising) that may link to or be accessible from this Website.

It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it, especially before providing any personal data through this Website. This Website is operated in and controlled from the United States of America. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Website, or if you wish to unsubscribe from Website services for which you have previously registered, please contact us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com) or at the address at the end of this policy.

**PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF SERVICE FOR THE WEBSITE CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO SUCH PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF SERVICE.**

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your sole choice is not to use this Website.

**TABLE OF CONTENTS.**

  1. Types of Information Collected
    * Personal Data
    * Aggregate and Anonymous Data
  2. Use of Cookies and Other Technologies
    * Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
  3. Our Use of Your Information
  4. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties
    * Disclosure to Affiliates
    * Disclosure to Third Parties
    * Disclosure to Others
  5. _Information We Receive From Third Parties_
  6. Links to Other Websites
  7. Your Choices
  8. Access and Correction
  9. Children and Privacy
  10. Message Boards, Chat Services, Blogs and Other User Forums
  11. Your California Privacy Right
  12. Data Security
  13. Exclusions
  14. Other Terms and Conditions
  15. Website Location
  16. Changes to this Privacy Policy
  17. Miscellaneous
  18. Interpretation
  19. Contacting Blumhouse.com Regarding Your Privacy

### 1\. Types of Information Collected.

Personal Data: Personally Identifiable Information (“Personal Data”) is any information that can be used to identify a specific individual, such as your name, email address, home address, phone number, _demographic information (such as zip code, age), location information, or payment information (such as account or_ credit card information). This Website collects Personal Data when you interact with this Website, for example when you subscribe for newsletters; register for membership services such as chat services or message boards; participate in chat services, blogs, messaging services, bulletin boards, message boards or other user forums; respond to polls or surveys; purchase products or services via this Website; register for sweepstakes, contests and other promotional opportunities; or seek help from our customer service departments. We also may collect information when you purchase products or services offline, or register for wireless services via your cellphone or other wireless devices (collectively, “Other Services”). Because providing detailed information regarding our Privacy Policy when you register or provide information in connection with these Other Services often proves impractical, you may instead be provided with a short notice that reminds you to refer to this Privacy Policy and other relevant information from us. We may also obtain Personal Data from reputable third parties, such as credit agencies.

**Aggregate and Anonymous Data:** Aggregate and anonymous data is information that does not identify you specifically, including data collected automatically through the operation of this Website (“AA Data”). We may collect Website usage data (such as which Website pages you visit and in what sequence) through the use of various technologies. For example, we collect IP addresses from individuals who visit this Website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from a website, its servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to any Personal Data, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to this Website and us. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and connection information such as browser type or version. During some visits, we may use software tools, such as JavaScript, to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page.  

### 2\. Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies.

Like many websites, we use “cookies” or other similar technologies to collect AA Data. A cookie is a small data file that writes to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes when you visit this Website. Cookies allow this Website to measure traffic activity on this Website and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, allowing you to visit “member only” portions of this Website without re-registering, and tracking the progress and number of entries in activities that require registration or entry, such as sweepstakes. Similarly, if you have asked us to send you information about upcoming products and promotions, using cookies we collect information about which Website pages you have visited and in what order (“Clickstream Data”) that may allow us to narrow or limit the materials provided to you based on your prior online activities or preferences. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent, as described below.

In addition, we may use a service that collects data remotely by using so-called “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar means (collectively, “Pixel Tags”) embedded in the Website’s content. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1×1), that is ordinarily not visible to Website visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors’ hard drives. This information is AA Data.

_To learn how you may be able to reduce the number of cookies you receive from us, or delete cookies that have already been installed in your browser’s cookie folder, please refer to your browser’s help menu or other instructions related to your browser. If you do disable or opt out of receiving cookies, we will honor your request, however please be aware that some content, functionality, services and features on this Website may not be available or work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your Blumhouse.com account. In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests._

_You can also learn more about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org, which includes additional, useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browsers_.

Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: Some content, functionality, services or features, including advertisements, on or available through this Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, licensors, service providers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies, alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies, to collect information about you when you use this Website. The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Data or they may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.  

### 3\. Our Use of Your Data.

  * We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Data:
  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account or subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data. For more information, see Your Choices.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we will not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Personal Data:** We will use your Personal Data for the purposes for which it was provided. For example, if you provide Personal Data to register for a newsletter or a text messaging service, to enter a contest or a sweepstake, or to purchase goods or services, we will use it to register you for or provide you with those goods or services. We may also use your Personal Data to provide you with information about features, products, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you. We also may send information or offers to selected groups of Website users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give those businesses your name or address. Under certain circumstances (for example, if you win a contest) we may post your Personal Data on this Website. We will notify you of this possibility when you provide the Personal Data and, if possible, when the Personal Data is posted.

Cookies and similar tools may be used to relate your use of this Website and AA Data to Personal Data obtained from you. If any AA Data is linked with Personal Data, the linked AA Data will then be treated as Personal Data.

**AA Data:** We may also use Personal Data in aggregate form for purposes of research or analysis. In order to better understand and serve the users of this Website and Other Services, Blumhouse.com often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Data we gather. Although this aggregated data may be based in part on Personal Data, it does not identify you personally. Blumhouse.com may share this type of AA Data with a variety of third parties, including its licensors, service providers, other current and prospective business partners, and agents

We may use AA Data collected from this Website for website administration, advertising and promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various unaffiliated entities for such purposes. For example, IP addresses are used for the purposes of system administration and to provide AA Data to advertisers about the volume of use on this Website, and Clickstream Data and demographic AA Data may be shared with our advertisers and other business partners. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows this Website to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on this Website. This data (including Clickstream Data about your activities on our Website) may be shared with these companies for this purpose.  

### 4\. Disclosure of Personal Data: Disclosure to Affiliates.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and other information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose Personal Data that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To contractors, content providers, product providers, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business [and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Data confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them].
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. [For example, if you give us an e-mail address to use the “e-mail a friend” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and your e-mail address to the recipients.]
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * Otherwise, with your consent.

We reserve the right to share Personal Data with our affiliates. If you do not want us to share your Personal Data with our affiliated companies for their marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by contacting us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com) (see “Your Choices” below).

**Disclosure to Third Parties:** Blumhouse.com, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf, such as hosting this Website or specific portions of this Website, maintaining databases, administering contests, providing wireless services, mailing information and processing payments. When we employ a third party to perform these functions, that third party will only be provided with the particular Personal Data it needs to perform its function, and is required to protect the Personal Data. For third-party sponsored sweepstakes, contests or promotions, we may request Personal Data from you that may be shared with the sponsor upon request.

**Disclosure to Others:  
**In addition, we may disclose Personal Data without providing you with a choice under the following limited circumstances to: (1) protect the legal rights, property, privacy or safety of Blumhouse.com or its directors, officers, employees, agents and contractors; (2) protect the legal rights, property, safety and security of visitors to our Website or other properties _and the public_ ; (3) protect against fraud, _security issues, technical issues_ or illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (4) respond to inquiries or requests from public authorities, such as law enforcement authorities; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; (6) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; (7) _respond to an emergency_ ; or (8) comply with any court order, law, rule, regulation, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

If Blumhouse.com sells all or part of this Website or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, we may, in our sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign your Personal Data to a third party as part of or in connection with that transaction. Upon such transfer, the privacy policy of the acquiring entity may govern the further use of your Personal Data.  

### 5\. Information we receive from third parties.

_We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from Blumhouse.com, that website will submit to us your email address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or feature (such as a Facebook or Twitter application or a similar application or feature on a third party website) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including AA Data and Personal Data, such as lists of your friends, “likes”, comments you have shared, groups and location. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections”, or information about you is otherwise accessible through your “connections” web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service. We may also receive information about you from third party data providers. We may supplement the information we collect about you through this Website with such information from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you or to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you._  

### 6\. Links to Other WEBSites.

_This Website may contain links to other websites that we do not own or operate. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors or business partners that may use our logos as part of a co-branding or co-marketing agreement. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these websites or their content, products, services or privacy policies or practices. These other websites may send their own cookies to your hard drive, they may independently collect data or solicit Personal Data and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. You should independently assess the authenticity of any website which appears or claims that it is part of our Website (including those linked to through an email or social networking page)._  

### 7\. Your Choices.

You can use this Website and certain Other Services without providing any Personal Data, but if you decline to provide Personal Data, you may not be able to access or use certain content, functionality, services or features. If you have previously provided Personal Data to this Website and have subscribed to one or more email newsletters or are receiving emails or other communications from this Website and you do not want to receive such emails, please discontinue your subscriptions by selecting the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any message, or contacting us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com). You may opt out of receiving offers from us by adjusting your Website preferences at our unsubscribe link. If you ask that we stop using your Personal Data, we will honor that request. However we will retain and use records of your Personal Data as needed in order to comply with applicable federal, state, local or international law, rules and regulations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements with you.  

### 8\. Access and Correction.

If you would like to review, correct, delete or change the Personal Data that you have previously provided us, please contact us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com). We will take reasonable steps to update, correct or delete Personal Data in our possession in accordance with such requests.

_In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain Personal Data you have submitted through this Website. We are under no obligation to store such Personal Data indefinitely and disclaim any liability or obligation arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such Personal Data. It may not always be possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons. We will endeavor to retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you access, content, functionality, services or features. We do not control certain privacy settings and preferences maintained by our social media partners, such as Facebook and Twitter. If you wish to make changes to those settings and preferences, you may do so by visiting the settings page of the appropriate social media website._  

### 9\. CHILDREN AND PRIVACY.

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the websites visited by their children. At various places on this Website or Other Services, we may ask users for their age. By using this Website or Other Services you agree to respond truthfully and accurately about your age.

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Children under the age of 13 are expressly prohibited from submitting or posting any Personal Data on this Website or Other Services. We do not knowingly collect, _use or disclose_ personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features or register on this Website, make any purchases of products or services through this Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, _we will make reasonable efforts_ to delete _such_ information _from our records_. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com).  

### 10\. Message Boards, Chat Services, Blogs and Other User Forums.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (collectively, “posted”) on public areas of this Website, or transmitted to other users of this Website or third parties (collectively “User Contributions”). Please remember that information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other user forums becomes public information _and is not subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy_. Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Use caution when posting. Individuals under the age of 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifiable information when participating in any area of this Website where postings might become public. Please see our Terms of Service for the standards of behavior that must be followed when using these portions of this Website or Other Services.

Although we limit access to certain pages and you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of this Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

If you delete your User Contributions from this Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on this Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Service.  

### 11\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com) or write us at: RSV BH LLC, 381 Park Avenue South, Suite 1201, New York, NY 10016.  

### 12\. Data Security Disclaimer.

Blumhouse.com takes reasonable security precautions to secure the Personal Data that you choose to provide through the Website against the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access of such information. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet _or storage of information_ is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Blumhouse.com to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your Personal Data, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any _information_ you transmit to us, _and you use this Website and provide us with your information at your own risk_. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures maintained on this Website. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by contacting us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com).

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  

### 13\. Exclusions.

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Blumhouse.com on or through this Website or Other Services (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). Please see our Terms of Service for our policies regarding such Unsolicited Information. All such Unsolicited Information shall be deemed not to be confidential, proprietary or secret, and Blumhouse.com will be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.  

### 14\. Other Terms and Conditions.

Your access to and use of this Website or Other Services is subject to the Terms of Service.  

### 15\. Applicable Law.

The Website is governed by and operated in, and in accordance with the laws, rules and regulations of, the United States, and are intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. Blumhouse.com makes no representation that this Website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of any other nation. By using this Website, or providing us with any information, you (a) acknowledge that this Website is subject to the laws, rules and regulations of the United States, (b) consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws, rules and regulations may not be as comprehensive as or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and (c) waive any claims that may arise under those laws. Please note that we do not represent or warrant that this Website is appropriate for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access this Website do so at their own initiative and are responsible for complying with all applicable laws, rules and regulations.  

### 16\. Changes to this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology, or changes in our policies and practices regarding information collection and use. If we make revisions to the way we collect or use Personal Data, we may provide notice of those changes by either: (1) announcing the change on the home page of this Website or (2) taking such other action as we deem appropriate under the circumstances, including without limitation, posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on this Website. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last Updated” legend at the top of this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through this Website. _We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for the latest information on our privacy policies and practices._ By continuing to use this Website following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, please do not continue using this Website.  

### 17\. MISCELLANEOUS.

The provisions of this Privacy Policy are subject to those provisions of this Website’s Terms of Service that may have any applicability to the provisions of this Privacy Policy.  

### 18\. INTERPRETATION.

Wherever used in this Privacy Policy, the following terms have the following meanings and interpretations, unless the context requires otherwise: “include”, “including” or any other variation of that word, and “for example” or “such as”, will each be deemed to be followed by the phrase: “, without limitation,”; “and” and “or” will each be deemed to mean “and/or”; and “person” will be deemed to mean any natural person and any entity.  

### 19\. Contacting Blumhouse.com Regarding Your Privacy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Personal Data gathered by this Website or Other Services, or about the operation of this Website or Other Services, or if you wish to unsubscribe from this Website or Other Services, please contact us at [privacy@bhdigital.com](mailto:privacy@bhdigital.com), or at the address listed below.

RSV BH LLC  
381 Park Avenue South, Suite 1201  
New York, NY 10016  
****
